MR. DOMENIC SANTANGELO

leader: full-stack engineer: technologist

contact domenics@gmail.com for full resume

Profile

Passionate, goal-oriented & driven technologist, experienced in global-level corporations. Thrives in technology organizations, loves talking with the Three Cs: Customers, Collaborators, and CxOs. From software architecture to implementation, I am a rare T-shaped contributor possessing a skill set that's both deep and wide.

I am a member of the exclusive eBay Inventor's Club for my contributions to eBay's patent portfolio.

Experience



iFixit: Director, Project Management & Engineering Manager; SLO, CA November 2016 - present

Reporting to the CEO, I am responsible for project management and product development for <u>ifixit.com</u>. I also lead the software engineering team.



Magento: MTS 2, Technical Engineering Manager; Campbell, CA November 2015 - 2016

I wore many hats at Magento, from people managing to product development, site architecture and coding.



eBay Enterprise: MTS 2 Lead Software Engineer, Architect; San Jose, CA January 2012 - 2015

My tenure at eBay Enterprise is best characterized by two concepts: operational excellence and modernization.



AAA NCNU: Web Application Developer IV; Emeryville, CA – 2010-2012Responsible for CSAA.com, our flagship site. Was most senior developer on staff and interim team manager.



WorkHabit, Inc: Director of Engineering; Sacramento, CA — 2007-2009

Built a top tech consultancy focused on Drupal & CMS solutions. Consulted for startups from Long Beach to Manhattan.

Education

University of California, Davis — Political Science, 2002-2006

Cuesta College, San Luis Obispo — AA, IGETC, 1998-2002